<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lasher.dev</title>
    <link>https://lasher.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lasher.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://lasher.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lasher.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lasher.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>about Current stack  Full stack MERN Jest and Mocha/Chai git docker gcloud jenkins scripting languages (bash, python, AppleScript) some C++ some UML  Career history Hobbies In a previous life I was an avid backpacker. Somewhere along the line I stopped backpacking and I missed it. I recently got back into it.
I am also a maker. I joined a makerspace in Broomfield so that I could have time and tools to work on personal projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lasher.dev/bookshelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lasher.dev/bookshelf/</guid>
      <description>Bookshelf Code: The Hidden Language of Computer Hardware and Software by Charles Petzold
Software Craftsman, The: Professionalism, Pragmatism, Pride by Sandro Mancuso
Refactoring: Improving the Design of Existing Code by Martin Fowler
C++ Coding Standards: 101 Rules, Guidelines, and Best Practices by Andrei Alexandrescu
The Elements of Computing Systems: Building a Modern Computer from First Principles by Noam Nisan and Shimon Schocken 
Digital Computer Electronics by Albert Malvino and Jerald Brown</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello world [again]</title>
      <link>https://lasher.dev/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lasher.dev/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>This is roughly my third iteration of my site. The first was essentially me shouting half baked ideas about software development into the void. The second was a repository for things that I need regularly but not often. Things like dot files for different types of machines, common shell commands that I don&amp;rsquo;t use everyday, and articles that cover questions that I sometimes get about the process of development.
I say &amp;ldquo;roughly&amp;rdquo; because as with many iterative processes, the transition from one category to the next is gradual with some regression and some spurts forward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
